http://www.exeteracademy.co.uk/privacy-statement

Exeter
Academy (which means Exeter Academy and their associated companies) is committed to protecting your privacy when you use our on-line, telephone or other services ("Services"). In this policy we explain how and why we collect your information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.
From time to time, we add or change functions, features or products to our Web Sites or add or change Services. This, and our commitment to protecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review any amendments.
Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to contact at Exeter Academy at Exeter Academy or alternatively see the section "Comments" below.
Your acceptance of these Privacy Statement termsBy using any of the sites within our web site network ("Web Sites") or our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
What data do we collect and how do we use it?Exeter Academy collects and processes information about you in order to:(i) identify you each time you visit a Web Site or wish to have a Service provided; (ii) process orders or applications submitted by you; (iii) improve our Services and Web Sites (iv) Customise your experience, for example, provide advertisements that we think are relevant to you and which support any specific requests for information you may make through keyword searches; (v) carry out research on the demographics, interests and behaviour of all of our customers; and (vi) send you information we think you may find useful, including information about new Exeter Academy products and services.
You may be asked, either when you register with us, or at other times, for information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences. In addition, when you order certain goods or services from our Web Sites, we will need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date.
You are under no obligation to provide this information, but if you don't then we may not be able to provide you with certain services or personalise your experience and tailor our Services for you (for example, tell you about special offers on things you're interested in).Log files/IP addressesWhen you visit our Web Sites, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognised by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web Sites and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.Non personal informationWe may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our Web Sites. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our Web Sites. We may from time to time supply the owners or operators of third party sites from which it is possible to link to our Web Sites with information relating to the number of users linking to our Web Sites from their sites. You cannot be identified from this information.
Use of CookiesCookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web Site if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user's computer, cookies do not personally identify customers or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.
We use cookies for the following reasons:
To identify who you are and to access your account information;
To estimate our audience size and patterns;
To ensure that you are not asked to register twice;
To control how often visitors see similar ads;
To track preferences and to improve and update our Web Site; and
To track the progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests.
With whom is the information shared? Exeter Academy will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party suppliers who provide services on our behalf and our inspectors or accreditation schemes.Exeter Academy may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our Web Site visitors and customers of our telephone services in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.Exeter Academy may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Exeter Academy and its Web Sites, visitors to the Web Sites and customers of our Services.Our Web Site contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. Exeter Academy is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites. We will only sell or rent your personal information to a third party either as part of a sale of the assets of a Exeter Academy company or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.Information about products and servicesIt is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. In order to help us do this, from time to time Exeter Academy companies may send you details of our products and services which we think may be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to receive these details, please e-mail us at Exeter AcademySecurityExeter Academy places a great importance on the security of all information associated with our customers. We have security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of customer data under our control. For example, our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorised personnel have access to user information. With regard to our Web Sites, we use secure server software (SSL) to encrypt financial information you input before it is sent to us. While we cannot ensure or guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we use our best efforts to prevent this.Where is the information stored?Information which you submit via our Web Sites or our telephone services is stored on a computer located in the European Economic Area. This is necessary in order to process the information and to send you any information you have requested. Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and to reputable third party suppliers, which may be situated outside the European Economic Area. Not all countries outside the EEA have data protection or privacy laws. In addition, if you use our Services while you are outside the EEA, your information may be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with those Services.
Your Rights
Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Data Protection Act 2018 (DPA) you have a number of rights with regard to your personal data. You have the right to request from us access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data ,the right to restrict processing , object to processing as well as in certain circumstances the right to data portability.
If you have provided consent for the processing of your data you have the right (in certain circumstances) to withdraw that consent at any time which will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent was withdrawn.
You have the right to lodge a complaint to the Information Commissioners' Office if you believe that we have not complied with the requirements of the GDPR or DPA18 with regard to your personal data.
CommentsPlease e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about our Privacy Policy to Exeter Academy .
Select LanguageEnglishAfrikaansAlbanianArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBulgarianCatalanChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CroatianCzechDanishDutchEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekHaitian CreoleHebrewHindiHungarianIcelandicIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseKoreanLatvianLithuanianMacedonianMalayMalteseNorwegianPersianPolishPortugueseRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSpanishSwahiliSwedishThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnameseWelshYiddish
Courses: General, IELTS, FCE, Business, Specialist, Medical, Over 50s
English courses for adults (18+) only    |    Privacy Statement    |    This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.    |    +44 1392 430303    |    Cookie Statement    |    Terms of Use
